Register of the Finnish Relief Fund records
Hoover Institution Archives
Finnish Relief Fund records
1939-1946
XX405
Hoover Institution Archives
240 manuscript boxes, 2 oversize boxes, 10 card file boxes (107 linear feet)
Correspondence, memoranda, minutes, reports, press releases, financial records, printed matter, memorabilia, and photographs relating to fundraising in the United States for civilian relief in Finland during the Russo-Finnish War.
Finnish Relief Fund.
Access
Microfilm use only (except for boxes 249-250 that have not been microfilmed).
Alternative Form Available
Also available on microfilm (207 reels).
Historical Note
(From Herbert Hoover, An American Epic, Volume IV)
In the Stalin-Hitler alliance of August 23, 1939, Stalin had exacted as part of his share in conquest the annexation of the helpless Baltic States. Estonia and Latvia complied with Stalin's demand for "protective garrisons." Lithuania was divided between Stalin and Hitler. Finland alone refused.
When Stalin attacked Finland on November 30, 1939, I made the following statement:
Civilization struck a new low with the Communists' attack on peaceful Finland. It is a sad day to every decent and righteous man and woman in the world. We are back to the morals and butchery of Ghengis Khan....
They [the Finns] will make a brave fight. They may be overwhelmed by the hordes whose morals are the morals of Communism; whose methods are cowardly. They are to be brought into subjection by the killing of defenseless women and children. Brave men do not do that. Even if Finland falls, the day will come when it will rise again -for the forces of righteousness are not dead in the world.
On December 3, the Finnish Minister to the United States, Hjalmar J. Procope, through my old associate, Lewis L. Strauss, asked if our group would undertake to organize relief for Finland as we were already doing for Poland. Before replying, I again, as in the case of Poland, urged Norman Davis, Chairman of the American Red Cross, that this relief be undertaken by that organization. I proposed that our group would serve under him if he wished. He decided the Red Cross would limit its services to medical aid and would collect garments through its chapters. However, Finland's most critical need was food.
Our old colleagues incorporated the Finnish Relief Fund, Inc., under the laws of Delaware on December 6, 1939. Except for part of the clerical help, this American organization consisted entirely of volunteers. The following officers were elected: Herbert Hoover, Chairman; Edgar Richard, President; Lewis L. Strauss, Vice-President; John Jay Hopkins, Vice-Chairman and Director of Organization. Additional Directors: Perrin C. Galpin, Frank C. Page, Raymond Sawtelle, Edwin P. Shattuck, John L. Simpson, H. Alexander Smith, Clare M. Torrey...
On December 7, I made the following address on Finnish relief:
America has a duty to do its part in the relief of the hideous suffering of the Finnish people. Our people should have an outlet in which to express their individual and practical sympathy. I have consented to organize a nation-wide Finnish Relief Fund for this purpose. I appeal to the American people for its support. Finland is not a rich country. The people have little reserve for emergency. They are making a heroic defense. Air attacks have compelled the evacuation of civilians from their towns and cities. Hundreds of thousands of women and children have been driven from their homes in the middle of northern winter...Others are without adequate shelter, clothing, and food. This Fund is for the purpose of serving these broad needs. The American Red Cross has appealed for funds to furnish medicines, hospital supplies, and many garments will be provided through their chapters. They should be supported. The two funds will cooperate fully...
To avoid overhead expenses, I addressed a telegram to the publishers of America's leading newspapers, asking whether they would receive contributions, report the donors in their columns, and remit the money to us. The press responded in extraordinary fashion -some 1,400 newspapers established such funds.
We organized the usual radio programs and theatrical benefits, issued press statements, and arranged public meetings....
In the spring of 1940, Congress appropriated $30,000,000 to aid the Finns. The total response from our public appeal was $3,546,526.11...
With great losses after a valiant defense against overwhelming Communist armies, the Finns agreed to terms of peace on March 12. Stalin forced them to surrender a large part of their fertile lands, from which 400,000 Finns were expelled almost overnight.
On March 13, I made this statement:
The terms imposed on Finland mark another sad day for civilization. The Finns have made a heroic defense that will live for all time. But the odds were insuperable. The Finnish Relief Fund must continue...
On the same day, we received the following cable from Kyosti Kallio, President of Finland:
We are deeply grateful to the Finnish Relief Fund for the humanitarian aid which we have received during the Finnish War for the relief of the distressed. I hope with all my heart that you will continue to alleviate the lot of those suffering on account of the war for the population of the ceded areas will be moving into the territory of the republic... We have signed a compulsory peace yet we hope that our struggle for the right has gained us the sympathy of the civilized world and trust that we shall not be left to our own resources in the work of reconstruction...
Scope and Content of Collection
Correspondence, memoranda, minutes, reports, press releases, financial records, printed matter, memorabilia, and photographs relating to fundraising in the United States for civilian relief in Finland during the Russo-Finnish War.
General Note
Finnish Relief Fund will be abbreviated throughout as FRF.
Finland.; International relief.; Russo-Finnish War, 1939-1940--Civilian relief.; United States--Foreign relations.; World War, 1939-1945--Civilian relief.; World War, 1939-1945--Finland.; World War, 1939-1945.
- Microfilm Reel Content Guide
  Downloadable PDF file of the Microfilm Reel Content Guide
- Chairman's File, 1939-1940
  Scope and Contents note
  Files of Herbert Hoover. Correspondence, speeches, statements, writings, minutes of meetings, and other records relating to FRF activity and food relief to Finland, arranged alphabetically by physical form
  - Appeals (Box 1)
    - To all editors of morning and afternoon papers, Typescript, 1939 December 8 (Folder 1)
    - To the American people for relief to Finland, as read by Herbert Hoover for the Paramount News Reel Service, Baltimore Hotel, Holograph and typescript, 1939 December 10 (Folder 2)
  - Cables
    - General
      - General
        - Incoming, 1939-1940 (Folder 3)
        - Outgoing, 1940-1941 (Folder 4)
      - Drafts of cable supporting a loan to Finland through Congress for non-military supplies. Typescript and holograph (Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous (Folder 6)
    - Cajander; Hynes; Kyosti; Kallio; Maverick, Robert; Ryti, Risto; Stephens, Dorsey; Tuck, Hallam, 1939-1941 (Folder 7)
    - Finnish Government
      - General, 1939-1941 (Folder 8)
      - Incoming, 1940-1941 (Folder 9)
    - Finnish Relief Fund (Box 2)
      - General
        - Incoming, 1939 December-1940 September (Folder 1)
        - Outgoing, 1939 December-1941 March (Folder 2)
      - Organization of Committee (Folder 3)
    - Stephens, Dorsey (FRF representative in Helsinki), 1939-1940 (Folder 4)
  - Correspondence
    - General
      - General (Folder 5)
      - Acknowledgments (Box 3)
        - General (Folder 1)
        - For Herbert Hoover's signature (Folder 2-10)
        - For Herbert Hoover's signature (Box 4, Folder 1-17)
      - Letters
        - Crank (Folder 18)
        - Of appreciation (Folder 19)
        - Of praise (Folder 20)
        - Processed (Folder 21)
        - Sent to state chairmen (Box 5)
          - General, 1940 April 13 (Folder 1)
          - Master file (Complete set) (Folder 2)
      - Miscellaneous (Folder 3)
    - Anonymous (Folder 4)
    - Groups and organizations
      - General
        - Industrial groups (Folder 5)
        - Religious groups (Folder 6)
        - Theatrical groups (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - American-Scandinavian Field Hospital Unit (Folder 2)
      - Red Cross. Includes annotations by Herbert Hoover (Folder 3)
    - Individuals
      - General
        - General (Folder 4-20)
        - General (Box 7, Folder 1-8)
      - Caroll, Philip H., Major (Folder 9)
      - Disque, Brice P. (Folder 10)
      - Hopkins, Jay (Folder 11)
      - Lundbeck, Hilmer G. (Folder 12)
      - Miller, Bernice (Folder 13)
      - O'Ryan, J.F. (Folder 14)
      - Rockefeller, Winthrop and John D., Jr. (Folder 15)
      - Selvage, James P. and Fred Smith (Folder 16)
      - Stoddard, Mary, Mrs. (Folder 17)
    - States
      - Alaska (Folder 18)
      - California (Folder 19)
      - Colorado (Folder 20)
      - Connecticut (Folder 21)
      - Delaware (Folder 22)
      - Illinois (Folder 23)
      - Louisiana (Folder 24)
      - Massachusetts (Folder 25)
      - Michigan (Folder 26)
      - Missouri (Folder 27)
      - Nebraska (Folder 28)
      - New Hampshire (Folder 29)
      - New York (Folder 30)
      - North Dakota (Folder 31)
      - Ohio (Folder 32)
      - Pennsylvania (Folder 33)
  - Financial records (Box 8)
    - General
      - General (Folder 1)
      - Expenses of FRF (Folder 2)
      - Quotes for states (Folder 3)
    - Finnish-American Trading Corporation (Folder 4)
  - Publicity file
    - Article on FRF. Boy Ranger, 1940 March (Folder 5)
    - Food program for Finland (Folder 6)
    - Press statements, 1939-1940 (Folder 7)
    - Speeches (Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous (Folder 9)
  - Reports
    - On coin collection box campaign for Herbert Hoover, Typescript, 1940 April 8 (Folder 10)
    - On FRF, Official report to Secretary of State. Typescript, 1940 February 15 (Folder 11)
    - On organizing FRF, Preliminary draft of the report written by Herbert Hoover, 1940 August 14 (Folder 12)
  - Special events file
    - Luncheon, Brooklyn, NY, 1940 February 21 (Folder 13)
    - Meetings
      - Elizabeth, NJ, 1940 February 23 (Folder 14)
      - Minneapolis, MN, 1939 February 29 (Folder 15)
    - Shows - Horse show, 1940 February 2 (Folder 16)
    - Trips
      - Detroit, MI, 1940 January 21 (Folder 17)
      - Harrisburg, PA, 1940, March 4 (Folder 18)
      - Peoria, Ill, 1940 February 14 (Folder 19)
      - Pittsburgh, PA, 1940 March 3 (Folder 20)
- State Chairmen's File, 1939-1940
  Cables, letters, directives, arranged alphabetically by physical form
  - General (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Cables, May, 1940 January- (Folder 2-6)
  - Directives to chairmen, including from Herbert Hoover (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Financial records (Folder 2)
  - Lists
    - State chairmen (Folder 3)
    - State representatives (Folder 4)
  - Sample letters and publicity material (Folder 5-6)
  - Subject file. Mostly correspondence
    - Canada (Folder 7)
    - Mexico (Folder 8)
    - Unites States
      - General - Western States
        - General (Folder 9)
        - Letters of appreciation signed by Herbert Hoover (Folder 10)
      - Alabama (Box 11)
        - General (Folder 1-2)
        - Clippings (Folder 3-6)
      - Alaska (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Arizona (Folder 2)
      - Arkansas (Folder 3-5)
      - California (Folder 6-7)
      - California (Box 13, Folder 1-2)
      - Colorado (Folder 3-6)
      - Connecticut (Box 14, Folder 1-3)
      - Delaware (Folder 4-5)
      - District of Columbia (Folder 6-7)
      - District of Columbia (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Florida (Folder 2-4)
      - Georgia (Folder 5-6)
      - Hawaii (Folder 7)
      - Idaho (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Illinois
        - General (Folder 2-6)
        - Chicago (Folder 7-8)
      - Indiana (Box 17, Folder 1-2)
      - Iowa (Folder 3-4)
      - Kansas (Folder 5-7)
      - Kentucky (Folder 8)
      - Louisiana (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
      - Maine (Folder 3-5)
      - Maryland (Folder 6-7)
      - Massachusetts (Box 19, Folder 1-4)
      - Michigan (Folder 5-7)
      - Minnesota (Box 20, Folder 1-3)
      - Mississippi (Folder 4)
      - Missouri (Folder 5-7)
      - Montana (Folder 8)
      - Nebraska (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Nevada (Folder 2-3)
      - New Hampshire (Folder 4)
      - New Jersey (Folder 5-8)
      - New Jersey (Box 22, Folder 1-2)
      - New Mexico (Folder 3)
      - New York
        - Atlantic seaboard (Folder 4)
        - Erie County (Folder 5)
        - New York City
          - General (Folder 6-10)
          - Arranged according to occupation or business (Box 23, Folder 1-3)
        - Upstate (Folder 4-7)
      - North Carolina (Folder 8)
      - North Dakota (Box 24, Folder 1-4)
      - Ohio (Folder 5-7)
      - Ohio (Box 25, Folder 1-2)
      - Oklahoma (Folder 3)
      - Oregon (Folder 4-6)
      - Oregon (Box 26, Folder 1-7)
      - Oregon (Box 27, Folder 1)
      - Pennsylvania (Folder 2-7)
      - Rhode Island (Box 28, Folder 1)
      - South Carolina (Folder 2-5)
      - South Dakota (Folder 6-7)
      - Tennessee (Box 29, Folder 1)
      - Texas (Folder 2-6)
      - Utah (Box 30, Folder 1-2)
      - Vermont (Folder 3)
      - Virginia (Folder 4)
      - Washington (Folder 5-6)
      - West Virginia (Folder 7)
      - West Virginia (Box 31, Folder 1-2)
      - Wisconsin (Folder 3-4)
      - Wyoming (Folder 5)
- Director's File, 1939-1940
  Papers of John Jay Hopkins, director of the Finnish Relief Fund, mostly correspondence and memoranda, arranged alphabetically by physical form
  - General. Includes memoranda (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Cablegrams (Folder 2)
  - Correspondence
    - General (Folder 3)
    - Hartigan, John (Folder 4)
    - State chairmen (second set) (Folder 5)
  - Forms
    - For divisional heads (Folder 6)
    - Sent to all state chairmen (Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous (Folder 8)
- Membership File, 1939-1947
  Telegrams, letters, lists, memoranda, minutes of meetings, and other records arranged alphabetically by name of members
  - General (Box 33)
    - Certificates of appreciation
      - Acknowledgments of (Folder 1-3)
      - Correspondence with state chairmen and others (Folder 4)
    - Form letters (Folder 5)
    - Lists of members (Folder 6)
    - Minutes of meetings (Board of Directors)
      - 1939 December 7 (Folder 7)
      - 1940
        - March 11 (Folder 8)
        - May 21 (Folder 9)
        - October 21 (Folder 10)
      - 1941 May 20 (Folder 11)
      - 1942 May 28 (Folder 12)
      - 1945
        - September 28 (Folder 13)
        - October 16 (Folder 14)
        - December 3 (Folder 15)
      - 1946 February 7 (Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous (Folder 17)
  - Fielder, Edward C. (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Galpin, Perrin (Folder 2)
  - Rickard, Edgar (Folder 3)
  - Saarinen, Eliel (Folder 4)
  - Sawtelle, Raymond (Folder 5)
  - Shattuck, Edwin (Folder 6)
  - Voorhees, Tracy (Folder 7)
- Office File, 1939-1947
  Agreements, correspondence, histories, legal documents, lists, personnel records, phone and postage records, subscriptions, arranged alphabetically by physical form
  - General. Bound volume of various documents relating to operations of the FRF (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Appeals from Finns regarding aid from FRF (Folder 2)
  - Broadcasting plan for all state chairmen (Folder 3)
  - By-laws (Folder 4)
  - Cables
    - General (Folder 5)
    - Incoming (Folder 6-7)
    - Outgoing (Box 36, Folder 1-2)
  - Certificates
    - Of incorporation (Folder 3)
    - Of thanks (Folder 4)
  - Chain letters (Folder 5)
  - Contributions file
    - General. Includes correspondence relating to donations (Folder 6-8)
    - Civic Service Organization Committee
      - American Legion (Folder 9)
      - Colonial Dames of America (Folder 10)
      - Daughters of the American Revolution (Folder 11)
      - Society of American Wars (Folder 12)
      - Veterans of Foreign Wars of the United States (Folder 13)
    - Fighting Funds for Finland, Inc. (Folder 14)
    - Finland. Consulate General (New York City) (Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1940-1946 (Box 37)
    - General
      - A (Folder 1)
      - B (Folder 2-3)
      - C (Folder 4-5)
      - D (Folder 6)
      - E (Folder 7)
      - F-G (Folder 8)
      - G (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - H (Folder 2)
      - I (Folder 3)
      - J (Folder 4)
      - K (Folder 5)
      - L (Folder 6)
      - M-O (Folder 7)
      - R (Folder 8)
      - S (Folder 9)
      - T (Folder 10)
      - U-W (Folder 11)
    - Cajander Committee (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Galpin, Perrin. Includes telegrams and miscellaneous printed matter (Folder 2-3)
    - Holsti, Rudolph. Includes miscellaneous correspondence about him (Folder 4-5)
    - Hopkins, John (Folder 6-7)
    - Maverick, Robert. Includes miscellaneous correspondence about him (Folder 8)
    - Maverick, Robert. Includes miscellaneous correspondence about him (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Muto, Frank (Folder 2)
    - Pohjala, Kyllikki. Includes miscellaneous material related to her (Folder 3-6)
    - Procope, Hjalmar (Folder 7)
    - Roosevelt, Eleanor (Folder 8)
    - Saari, John (Folder 9)
    - Spaar, Peter (Folder 10)
    - Spellman, Francis (Folder 11)
    - Strauss, Lewis (Folder 12)
    - Toivola, Urho (Folder 13)
    - Voorhees, Tracy (Folder 14)
    - Walsh, Edmund (Folder 15)
  - Filing papers (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Inquiries (Folder 2)
  - Instructions to state chairmen (Folder 3)
  - Leases
    - Graybar building (Folder 4)
    - Madison Square Garden (Folder 5)
  - Letterheads and other forms used by FRF (Folder 6)
  - Liquidation papers
    - General (Folder 7)
    - Cancellation of subscriptions (Folder 8)
  - Lists
    - Division directors (Folder 9)
    - Members. See Membership File/Lists
    - Recipients of certificates of appreciation (Folder 10)
    - State chairmen (Folder 11)
  - Memoranda and inter-office correspondence
    - General (Folder 12-13)
    - Rickard, Edgar (Folder 14)
    - Sawtelle, Raymond (Folder 15)
    - Stephens, Dorsey (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Permit for general solicitation (to collect money) (Folder 2)
  - Personnel records
    - General (Folder 3)
    - Employment applications (Folder 4-5)
    - Insurance records for employees of FRF (Folder 6)
    - Offers of service
      - General
        - General (Folder 7)
        - 1939 December-1940 January (Folder 8)
        - March, 1940 February- (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - A-E (Folder 2)
      - F-L (Folder 3)
      - M-Z (Folder 4)
      - Miscellaneous (Folder 5)
    - Subject file. Mostly application forms
      - Unit for Service in Finland (American Scandinavian Hospital) (Folder 6)
      - Volunteers for service in Finnish Army (Folder 7)
      - Wages of employees in New York State (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Phone records (Folder 2)
  - Postage records
    - General (Folder 3)
    - Correspondence
      - Postal Telegraph Company (Folder 4)
      - Postmaster, Grand Central Station (Folder 5)
      - Telegraph companies (Folder 6)
  - Sponsors file
    - Mayors who were requested to act as sponsors for FRF (Folder 7)
    - National Committee of Sponsors
      - General (Folder 8)
      - Correspondence (Folder 9)
      - Lists (Folder 10)
  - Subject file - Organization of FRF
    - General (Folder 11)
    - Plan (Folder 12)
    - Policy (Folder 13-15)
    - Staff (Folder 16)
    - Structure (Folder 17)
  - Suggestions received
    - General
      - General
        - 1939 December-1940 January (Folder 18)
        - 1940 (Box 45)
          - February (Folder 1)
          - March (Folder 2)
      - Ending war in Europe (Folder 3)
      - Finns settling in Alaska (Folder 4)
      - Munitions and arms for Finns (Folder 5)
      - Stamp sale (Folder 6)
    - Individuals
      - A-F (Folder 7)
      - G-L (Folder 8)
      - M-Z (Folder 9)
  - Telegrams
    - General (Folder 10)
    - A (Folder 11)
    - B (Folder 12)
    - C (Folder 13)
    - D (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - E (Folder 2)
    - F (Folder 3)
    - G (Folder 4)
    - H (Folder 5)
    - I-J (Folder 6)
    - K (Folder 7)
    - L (Folder 8)
    - M (Folder 9)
    - N (Folder 10)
    - O (Folder 11)
    - P-R (Folder 12)
    - S (Folder 13)
    - T (Folder 14)
    - U-V (Folder 15)
    - W (Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous (Folder 17)
- Correspondence File, 1939-1946
  Letters sent and received by the FRF. Includes correspondence with individuals, groups and organizations, the Finnish consulate and embassy in the United States, arranged alphabetically by category of correspondent and thereunder alphabetically by name
  - General (Box 47)
    - A-S (Folder 1-10)
    - S-Z (Box 48, Folder 1-5)
  - Groups and organizations
    - American Committee to Aid Finland (Folder 6)
    - American Federation of Labor (Folder 7)
    - American Red Cross (Folder 8)
    - American Scandinavian National Committee (Folder 9)
    - American Society of Civil Engineers (Folder 10)
    - American Youth Congress (Folder 11)
    - Aviation Service Commission (Folder 12)
    - Athletic Committee (Folder 13)
    - Canady Cooler Company (Folder 14)
    - Chambers of commerce (Folder 15)
    - Children's Crusade for Children (Folder 16)
    - Clubs and orders
      - General (Folder 17)
      - Business clubs (Folder 18)
      - Republican Club (Folder 19)
    - Community Chests and Councils (Folder 20)
    - Farm organizations (Folder 21)
    - Finland (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Finland. Consul General (New York City), 1939-1941 (Folder 2)
    - Finland. Legation (United States) (Folder 3)
    - Finland. Minister to the United States (Folder 4)
    - Finland Day Committee (Folder 5)
    - Finnish American Committee (Folder 6)
    - Finnish American Trading Corporation (Folder 7)
    - Finnish Red Cross (Folder 8)
    - Finnish Travel Information Bureau (Folder 9)
    - For Finland, Inc. (Folder 10)
    - Foundations helping Finland (Folder 11)
    - Friends Service Committee (Folder 12)
    - Governors (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - K. Phillips Morgan (Folder 2)
    - Labor Press Associates (Folder 3)
    - Mannerheim Child Welfare League (Folder 4)
    - National Information Bureau (Folder 5)
    - National Reform Organization ("Wings for Finland Fund") (Folder 6)
    - National Retail Dry Goods Association (Folder 7)
    - Negroes (Folder 8)
    - Newspaper editors (Folder 9)
    - Nurses (Folder 10)
    - The President's Committee on War Relief Agencies (Folder 11)
    - Rotary International Foundation (Folder 12)
    - Salvation Army (Folder 13)
    - Scandinavian Fraternity. Includes miscellaneous organizations (Folder 14)
    - Survey Associates (Folder 15)
    - Telephone Company (Folder 16)
    - United States. Department of State (Folder 17)
    - United States. Department of Treasury
      - Incoming
        - General
          - General tax exemptions (Folder 18)
          - Federal tax exemptions (Folder 19)
          - Individual tax exemptions (Folder 20)
        - New York City tax exemptions (Box 51, Folder 1)
        - New York state tax exemptions (Folder 2)
      - Outgoing (Folder 3)
    - Young Men's Christian associations (Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous (Folder 5)
  - Individuals
    - Bane, Suda L. (Folder 6)
    - Handerson, Frank and Elizabeth (Folder 7)
    - Hopkins, Jehn J. (Folder 8)
    - Hynes, John (Folder 9)
    - Jutila, K. T. (Finnish minister) (Folder 10)
    - Kuusamo, Kaarlo (Folder 11)
    - Lindberg, Otto G. (Folder 12)
    - Maenpaa, Nancy M. (Folder 13)
    - O'Ryan, John F. (Folder 14)
    - Prentiss Terry (FRF investigator in Finland) (Folder 15)
    - Ramsay, V. (Folder 16)
    - Selvage, James P. (Folder 17)
    - Tuck, Hallam (representative in Helsinki) (Folder 18-20)
    - Van Loon, Hendrik Willem (Folder 21)
  - Miscellaneous (Folder 22)
- Publicity Division File, 1939-1946